{
    "id": "18649623ec4c4d10ae3908507740692a",
    "title": "Sentence transformation: affirmative to negative",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3b11042ef00c423e9b51b01f4cecf377",
            "title": "Affirmative To Negative",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "My sister ....................................... not live with my parents.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................. not know the answer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ........................................ not want to leave now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My mother ........................................... not work at a bank.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Supriya ............................................... not sing very well.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Martin .................................................. not get along with his brother-in-law.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy .............................................. not kill the spider with his shoe.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "does",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She .................................... not recognize him at once.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ....................................... not apologize for his conduct.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She .............................................. not throw a tantrum when she was told that she wouldnâ€™t be able to go.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}